You know, whether you like me or not, I've dedicated my entire life to the advancement and the love of Black people.
And I have spent this week and my entire life being excoriated for maybe not always having the best delivery or not being able to maybe put my emotions into the space in the best way possible.
This week in particular, I watched as members of the Black community and Black media happily have castigated me publicly for simply saying that I feel I deserve to be in spaces that I've poured into.
I've also watched Black media in this same time frame platform individuals who have dedicated their lives to being anti-Black and perpetuating white supremacy.
I deserve to be protected and appreciated.
I hope that those of you who found it in your space to speak of me in such vitriol, though I've never brought it to you, I hope that you take time to do the self-exploration that you're suggesting that I do.
And there are private apologies and thank yous and love and that is appreciated.
But it does sting that it's never as loud as the public cacophony, but they are happy to receive from me.
Which says to me, Amanda, go where you are loved.
So you can catch me on my Patreon.
The SEAL Squad is where I'll be.
This work is very difficult, even when you take Lexapro.
This work is very difficult, even when you take care of me, you can catch me on my Patreon.
Okay!